A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Administration - Officers Files, SG 1, Series 2 FA390
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Quigg Newton Files, 3
  - Harkness Fellowships - Dinner - Commonwealth Fund 50th Anniversary, October 24, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 154)
  - Harkness Fellowships - Dinner - Dainton, Frederick and Frank Thistlethwaite, April 2, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 155)
  - Harkness Fellowships - Dinner - Fellows Arrival Dinners, 1975-1976 (Box 19, Folder 156)
  - Harkness Fellowships - Dinner - Robson, H. N., May 3, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 157)
  - Harkness Fellowships - Dinner - Trend, Lord and Lady, April 7, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 158)
  - Harkness Fellowships - Dinner - Woodroofe, Ernest G., October 28, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 159)
  - Harkness Fellowships - Division Correspondence, January 1, 1967-December 31, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 160)
  - Harkness Fellowships - Division Correspondence, January 1, 1967-December 31, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 161)
  - Harkness Fellowships - Division Correspondence, January 1, 1967-December 31, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 162)
  - Harkness Fellowships - Division Correspondence, January 1, 1967-December 31, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 163)
  - Harkness Fellowships - Division Correspondence, January 1, 1967-December 31, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 164)
  - Harkness Fellowships - Division Correspondence, January 6, 1970-December 18, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 165)
  - Harkness Fellowships - Division Correspondence, January 6, 1970-December 18, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 166)
  - Harkness Fellowships - Division Correspondence, January 6, 1970-December 18, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 167)
  - Harkness Fellowships - Division Correspondence, January 6, 1970-December 18, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 168)
  - Harkness Fellowships - Division Correspondence, January 6, 1970-December 18, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 169)
  - Harkness Fellowships - Division Correspondence, January 6, 1970-December 18, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 170)
  - Harkness Fellowships - Division Correspondence, January 6, 1970-December 18, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 171)
  - Harkness Fellowships - Division Correspondence, January 4, 1974-July 2, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 172)
  - Harkness Fellowships - Division Correspondence, January 4, 1974-July 2, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 173)
  - Harkness Fellowships - Division Correspondence, January 4, 1974-July 2, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 174)
  - Harkness Fellowships - Division Correspondence, January 4, 1974-July 2, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 175)
  - Harkness Fellowships - Division Staff, September 2, 1966-April 2, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 176)
    Restricted - Confidential material.
  - Harkness Fellowships - Fellowship Review, December 13, 1973-February 22, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 177)
  - Harkness Fellowships - Fellowship Review, December 13, 1973-February 22, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 178)
  - Harkness Fellowships - Fellowship Review, December 13, 1973-February 22, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 179)
  - Harkness Fellowships - Meeting, September 10, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 180)
  - Harkness Fellowships - Meeting, September 10, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 181)
  - Harkness Fellowships - Meeting, September 10, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 182)
  - Harkness Fellowships - Policy Reports (Quigg Newton), November 12, 1965; November 9, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 183)
  - Harkness Fellowships - Reinstatement - London Office Correspondence, May 10-18, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 184)
  - Harkness Fellowships - Reinstatement - Miscellaneous Correspondence, April 2, 1968-November 4, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 185)
  - Harkness Fellowships - Staff Visits, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 186)
  - Harkness Fellowships - Unfinished Business, May 26, 1969-May 1, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 187)
- Barry C. Smith Files, 4
  - Aldrich, Malcolm P. (Commonwealth Fund Board Member), December 9, 1925-July 30, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 188)
  - Aldrich, Malcolm P. (Commonwealth Fund Board Member), December 9, 1925-July 30, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 189)
  - American Medical Association, December 28, 1926-March 16, 1938 (Box 23, Folder 190)
  - Austrian Relief, October 2, 1922-November 17, 1922 (Box 23, Folder 191)
  - Bannard, Otto (Commonwealth Fund Board Member), May 1, 1922-January 15, 1929 (Box 23, Folder 192)
  - Birdsall, William E. (Commonwealth Fund Board Member), December 18, 1942-May 11, 1949 (Box 23, Folder 193)
  - Bunnell, Phil W. (Commonwealth Fund Board Member), June 14, 1940-December 2, 1946 (Box 23, Folder 194)
  - Child Welfare, 1921-1943 (Box 23, Folder 195)
  - Estimated Income of the Commonwealth Fund, 1933-1937 (Box 23, Folder 196)
  - Executive Committee - Correspondence and Memos, February 21, 1919-May 25, 1926 (Box 23, Folder 197)
  - Executive Committee - General, January 5, 1927-August 13, 1940 (Box 23, Folder 198)
  - Executive Committee - Minutes and Correspondence, September 21, 1921-December 28, 1939 (Box 23, Folder 199)
  - Farrand, Max (Commonwealth Fund Board Member), February 19, 1919-June 17, 1945 (Box 23, Folder 200)
  - Fisher, Samuel H. (Commonwealth Fund Board Member), March 5, 1919-November 5, 1942 (Box 24, Folder 201)
  - Fisher, Samuel H. (Commonwealth Fund Board Member), March 5, 1919-November 5, 1942 (Box 24, Folder 202)
  - Harkness, Edward Stephen, May 29, 1919-March 15, 1940 (Box 24, Folder 203)
  - Harkness, Edward Stephen, May 29, 1919-March 15, 1940 (Box 24, Folder 204)
  - Harkness, Edward Stephen, May 29, 1919-March 15, 1940 (Box 24, Folder 205)
  - Harkness, Edward Stephen - Cash Fund for Emergency Relief-Richardson, December 11, 1922-December 3, 1923 (Box 24, Folder 206)
  - Harkness, Edward Stephen - Moore, Gertrude, April 2, 1919-December 28, 1921 (Box 24, Folder 207)
  - Harkness, Edward Stephen - Russian Refugee Fund-Bakeman, April 19, 1923-December 26, 1923 (Box 24, Folder 208)
  - Harkness Report - Girls' Service League of America, May 17, 1948-June 21, 1948 (Box 24, Folder 209)
  - Harkness Report - Sister Elizabeth Kenny Foundation, Inc., December 10, 1947-December 17, 1948 (Box 24, Folder 210)
  - Harkness Report - Lenox Hill Neighborhood Association, Inc., June 12, 1944-March 14, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 211)
  - Harkness Report - Medical and Surgical Relief Committee of America, October 25, 1947-January 28, 1948 (Box 24, Folder 212)
  - Harkness Report - New Hampshire Society for Crippled Children and Handicapped Persons, August 19, 1947-November 3, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 213)
  - Harkness Report - New York Academy of Medicine, November 11, 1922-November 5, 1947 (Box 25, Folder 214)
  - Harkness Report - Physical Rehabilitation Foundation, February 6, 1946-February 9, 1948 (Box 25, Folder 215)
  - Harkness Report - Students International Union, October 16, 1947-December 2, 1947 (Box 25, Folder 216)
  - Harkness Report - Trudeau Sanatorium, April 15, 1947-May 24, 1947 (Box 25, Folder 217)
  - Harkness Report - Turtle Bay Music School, Inc., May 20, 1947-June 11, 1947 (Box 25, Folder 218)
  - Harkness Report - Urban League Service Fund, April 29, 1947-September 8, 1947 (Box 25, Folder 219)
  - Harkness Report - Yale Psychoclinic, February 9, 1925-March 30, 1925 (Box 25, Folder 220)
  - Hospital Management, September 20, 1919-April 24, 1925 (Box 25, Folder 221)
  - Kingsley, William M. (Commonwealth Fund Board Member), February 17, 1921-October 21, 1952 (Box 25, Folder 222)
  - Legal Research Committee, April 2, 1948 (Box 25, Folder 223)
  - Lovett, Robert A. (Commonwealth Fund Board Member), April 11, 1935-May 14, 1947 (Box 25, Folder 224)
  - Massie, Adrian (Commonwealth Fund Board Member), September 22, 1942-March 30, 1946 (Box 25, Folder 225)
  - Medical-Psychiatric Conference, July 31, 1947 (Box 25, Folder 226)
  - Mental Health in England, March 7-14, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 227)
  - Midcentury White House Conference on Youth, September 19-22, 1949 (Box 25, Folder 228)
  - Morrow, Dwight W. (Commonwealth Fund Board Member), January 19, 1926-November 28, 1930 (Box 25, Folder 229)
  - Murray, George Welwood (Commonwealth Fund Board Member), October 24, 1918-December 1, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 230)
  - Neurology, May 7, 1920-October 18, 1920 (Box 25, Folder 231)
  - New York Committee on the Study of Hospital Internships and Residencies, October 4-5, 1943 (Box 25, Folder 232)
  - Reconstruction Work in Europe, June 9, 1919-June 26, 1920 (Box 25, Folder 233)
  - Retention Schedule for Commonwealth Fund Files, March 21, 1947-April 3, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 234)
  - Sage, Dean (Commonwealth Fund Board Member), December 12, 1930-November 10, 1943 (Box 25, Folder 235)
  - Smith, Jeremiah, Jr. (Commonwealth Fund Board Member), October 17, 1929-March 14, 1935 (Box 25, Folder 236)
  - Yale University - Mental Health, June 8, 1948-October 23, 1948 (Box 25, Folder 237)